[Music] I'm
[Música]
going to put you in a little context about the
os voy a poner un poco en contexto de lo
subject energy in energy no energy
del tema energía en energía no
energy I don't know how
energía no sé cómo lo pronuncian los
others pronounce it energy energy energy energy
demás energía energía energía energía
okay it's a type that has been put that has
vale es un tipo que se ha puesto que se
become very viral especially in tick
ha hecho muy viral sobre todo en tick
tock okay but above all this has not
tock vale pero sobre todo esto no se ha
gone viral in tick tock for drinking
hecho viral en tick tock por beber
drinks
bebidas
how good it looks in the intro of the other one
qué bien se ve en la intro de la otro
today I don't like what do you think is going to
hoy no me van que te crees que va a
change I put the good one
cambiar he puesto la buena
seriously it just crossed your
en serio se te acaba de pasar por la
mind that
cabeza eso
in the guide in the guide
en el guía en el guía
as a travel route
como vía de viaje
energy energy well I mean it's a payment
energía energía bueno o sea es un pago
that has become very fashionable and that here there is
que se ha puesto muy de moda y que aquí
a dialogue there in fact
hay un diálogo hay de hecho
vera
vera
came out of the guaire river
salió del río guaire
came out in the wine river
salió en el río wine
[Music] that's
[Música]
why I didn't understand that reference
por eso no entendía esa referencia
the
los
steps of the game
pasos de juego
this
esto
is not
no es
that giving everything
que dando todo
oh
ay
[Music]
[Música]
look how bad god abused
fíjate que es malísimo dios abusado de
energy drinks
bebidas energéticas
are very bad I have brands that
sean malísimos yo hay marcas las que
have these big cans and such that
tienen las latas estas grandes y tal que
I can't drink I sit down I
yo no puedo beber me sienta me pongo me
get outbreaks indirectly I get
dan brotes indirectamente me pongo
very bad okay it was done  famous for ovens
malísimo vale se hizo famoso por hornos
and reds laughing at him of course well
y tintos los riéndose de él claro bueno
all these people are reacting to
toda esta gente está reaccionando a
his video for example here
vídeo suyo por ejemplo aquí
Oslo made a video on his channel
oslo le hizo un vídeo en el canal suyo
Oslo has a whole video okay here what I
oslo tiene un vídeo entero vale aquí lo
saw in a gesture of Iowa that it seems to me
visto en un gesto de iowa que me parece
that when he is recording that
que cuando está grabando esa
when he records the scene look at this
cuando graba la escena mira de esto
Juan I'm glad you liked
juan me alegro que te haya gustado mucho
the video a lot man we have dedicated a lot of game
el vídeo tío hemos dedicado mucho juego
that I'm going to respond to several
que le voy a responder a varios
acquaintances
conocidos
of these times that these people fall
de estas veces que a esta gente le cae
thanks to someone because it has become
gracias a alguien porque se ha puesto de
fashionable and that's why they find it funny because
moda y por eso les cae en gracia porque
I was watching the thing of the shot
yo estaba viendo el cosa del tiro
and the guy thanks doesn't have any or
y el tío gracias no tiene ninguno o sea
in fact he
de hecho
looked shady
se le veía turbio las bebidas
energy drinks are healthy
energéticas son saludables
I say what the [ __ ]
digo que
we have audio audio images of
tenemos audio audio imágenes de las
healthy energy drinks
bebidas energéticas saludables
one thing is that you go I
una cosa es que tú te vas yo lo mejor me
drink the best once every three weeks every month and
bebo una vez cada tres semana cada mes y
one day that I am very tired and tired
un día que estoy muy cansado y cansado
that I need to talk night what is for
que necesito charla noche lo que es para
the best I drink one okay but drinking tea
lo mejor me bebo una vale pero beber té
a drink daily okay these cans these cans
una bebida diaria vale estas latas estas
man these mice god this is
latas tío estos ratones dios esto es
brass please it is
latones por favor
very dangerous totally
es muy peligroso totalmente
totally the
totalmente
dangerous thing is  that energy drinks
lo peligroso es que la bebida energética
can help your heart improve
te pueden dar algo el corazón a la
circulation, not the game, smoking is a
circulación no el juego fumar es otra
different thing,
movida diferente
what the [ __ ]?
ya qué
Well, the guy with the guy, for some
bueno pues el tío con el tío por alguna
reason, he's addicted to drinking and he
razón pues es un adicto a la bebida y él
uploads videos to commented texts of all the
sube vídeos a textos comentados de todos
flavors there are, the mixtures there are, I
los sabores que hay las mezclas que hay
don't know what, I don't know how much, he says that he
no sé qué no sé cuánto él dice que él
was a kid who did a lot, thank you very much for the
era un chaval que le hacía mucho muchas
message, how dangerous it is that he's
gracias del mensaje lo peligroso que
not watching today because today for the
que no está hoy viendo porque hoy para
news, well, he was watching tell me
el noticiero pues estaba viendo dígame
who this guy is, no, and the message that they
quién es este tío no y el mensaje que le
gave him has been a person who was
dan ha sido una persona
a person who has been
que era ha sido una persona que durante
brutally bullying him his entire life, let's
brutal
see if I get carried away,
a ver si me carga aire
throughout his life they have done that they have brutally
durante toda la vida han hecho que le
bullied him his entire life
han hecho toda la vida un bullying
until he drank energy ideas, he
brutal hasta que bebió ideas energéticas
anticipates, thank you very much for the
anticipa muchas gracias por el de
cereal with a motor, seriously,
cereales con motor en serio
seriously, I
en serio
don't know, I saw that there's a video about an oven,
no sé yo vi que hay un vídeo de horno
etc.,
etcétera
this account slips away from me tick tock
esta cuenta a mí se me resbala tick tock
productively lately I see tick
productivamente últimamente veo tick
tock sector and there's this guy literally
tock sector y hay este tío literalmente
his content is pro, just like my
su contenido es pro así como mi
content is for work and we see that already, tell you
contenido es por trabajo y vemos que ya
that he smokes, smokes, smokes, smokes,
deciros que fuma fuma fuma fuma fuma
twitter joke  twitter comedy smoking is wrong it
twitter broma twitter comedia está mal
gives penis and ass cancer don't
fumar da cáncer de y de culo no
smoke
fuméis
this is pro I did
este es pro
n't find it funny at all god I do
no me ha hecho nada de gracia eso dios
n't know if I'm getting too old a
no sé si me estoy volviendo muy viejo
party pooper or what
muy aguafiestas o que dio
but I didn't find this
pero no me ha hecho ni gracia esta
intro funny at all not in an ironic way or in
intro ni de forma irónica de ni de
any way
ninguna
ironic or in any way
de forma irónica de de ninguna
sad I've said it many times I say
sad yo ya lo he dicho muchas veces digo
the human body
el cuerpo humano
this is the cereals nothing better I
este es el de los cereales nada mejor
feel the look I
siento la pinta
mean the body we have is a body
o sea el cuerpo que tenemos es un cuerpo
for life
para toda la vida
the body we have a body for
el cuerpo que tenemos un cuerpo para
life
toda la vida
our humor
nuestro humor
well if it's humor
bueno si es el humor
sarcasm doesn't look like giving thanks
el sarcasmo no pinta dar gracias
then normal the day is paid for the grandmother
pues normal el día se paga la abuela
after drinking zinc like esther
después de beber de zinc como esther
blanco please
blanco por favor
please I mean this is the bucket
por favor es decir que este es el cubo
of poop that is in her room they say it
de kaká que tiene su habitación dicen
's the bucket of pee that is under
que es el cubo de pis que tiene debajo
the bed please
de la cama por favor
after losing a round of the two
después de perder una ronda de los dos
literally friend
literal amiga
if you haven't done a bottle I'm not
si no habéis hecho una botella no soy
first really sorry gamer check
primero de verdad lo siento gamer check
bottle or days women israel etc
botella o días mujeres israel etc
if you
i
know me I'll quit whenever I want I'll quit
me conoces lo dejo cuando quiera lo dejo
whenever I want he stole 20 euros from her
cuando quiera le ha robado 20 euros el
bag to your mother to buy you the
bolso a tu madre para comprarte el
green tea monster
monster de té verde
but
pero
I hope to win
ojalá ganar
variant we know in person because
variante conocemos en persona porque al
apparently and also according to what I tell you in more
parecer y además según os cuento con más
detail in the news and as
detalles en el noticiero y según
explained by this other guy that
expuesto este otro tipo que
this guy who was to
este tipo que era
give me the name of the chat give me the
a ponerme el nombre del chat ponerme el
name of the red wine chat what I would
nombre del chat del tinto qué
love to see all of these when
me encantaría ver a todos estos cuando
they are 40 if they continue doing what they
tengan 40 como sigan haciendo lo que
do now they
hacen ahora
will not be even close to the same as
no estarán ni iu ni por asomo igual que
you and me who
tú y que yo
seems to have none of that
que parece que tenemos nada de ello
precisely
precisamente
cappa cappa well they have had a
cappa capa capa pues han tenido un
debate they have had a debate live
debate han tenido un debate en directo
ok and the debate has become a
ok y el debate pues se ha convertido en
trend ok
tendencia ok
energy is recognizing live that
energía está reconociendo en directo que
he likes to have relationships with kids
le gusta tener relaciones con chavales
younger than him to have power and that he
menores que él para tener poder y que le
likes them to have a childish appearance of
gusta que tengan apariencia infantil de
lol and well
lol y bueno
this is the progress of the
este es el progreso del sindicato de
youtube union we will have to see if what
youtube habrá que ver si lo que ha dicho
action has said or not energy trying to fix
acción o no energía intentando arreglar
the controversy because he is the pedophile is an
la polémica porque es el pedófilo es una
illness and being a woman not
enfermedad y ser mujer no
the sister of energy going to visit him in
la hermana de energía yendo a visitarle
jail with four monsters
a la cárcel con cuatro monsters
hidden in the rest
escondidas en el resto
energy flirting with minors more has a
energía ligando con menores más tiene
girlfriend
novia
the turkey
el pavo
this I don't know  if he will have put it successfully
esto no sé si lo habrá metido éxito bien
in the
en el
[Music]
[Música]
news to see if he was already sending me
noticiero a ver si ya me estaba mandando
okay but the guy the thing is that the guy
vale pero el tío la cosa es que el tío
starts flirting with girls okay 16
se pone a ligar con niñas vale de 16
years old and things like that but on top of that he had a
años y cosas así pero encima tenía la
girlfriend on low as if he wanted to
novia a la baja como si como queriendo
make them accomplices in cheating on his girlfriend it's
hacerlas cómplices de engañar a la novia
called more
se llama más
taking away apart that if not
quitando aparte que sino
infidelity not loyalty
la infidelidad no la de lealtad el
cricket I
cricket
wanted to stop taking pills for
quise dejar las pastillas para la
depression and I consumed a lot of red bull two
depresión y consumí mucha red bull dos
years later I almost died not only my
años después casi muero no solo el
heart but also my kidneys etcetera the
corazón también los riñones etcétera los
kidneys
riñones
the kidneys
los riñones
the bet has been made the guy admits that they
la apuesta se ha hecho el tío admita que
were accusing him of delegating with
le estaban acusando de delegar con
minors
menores
no no
no no
I just got an ad for the sabe the
me acaba de salir un anuncio del sabe
children in the energy live
the children en el directo de energía
this man of yours my twitter is reduced to
este hombre tuyo mi twitter se reduce a
energy and they see me the same but I don't
energía y me ven igual pero yo no
understand why they have made a turn in
entiendo por qué se han hecho virar en
the Jordi White memes in the last
los memes de jordi white en la última
hour that comes out to the media he justified you
hora que sale a los medios justificó me
are screwing my [ __ ] life you
estáis jodiendo la vida
are screwing my [ __ ] life
me estáis jodiendo la vida
see let's see the debate let's see the
a ver vamos a ver el debate a ver el
debate it's very  long but it depends on how it is we
debate es muy largo pero depende de cómo
will see the whole thing it's not worth it I don't
esté lo veremos entero no vale yo
know if I don't know if the debate is here in its
no sé si no sé si el debate está aquí
entirety it's to remove the 43 minutes I don't
entero es para quitar el 43 minutos no
know if it will be him but it's better but it depends
sé si será él pero más vale pero depende
on how it is well we will see it more in its entirety
de cómo esté pues lo veremos más enteros
less in its entirety no no no no no
menos entero no no
you don't know anything about my relationship okay
tú no sabes nada de mi relación vale
the animal
el animal
[Music]
[Música]
where
donde
the video also exists I'm going to put it they
además existe el vídeo lo voy a poner
downloaded it for a second while we
descargaron un segundo mientras que
watch the debate do not believe in Dallas or
vemos el debate no se cree en dallas o
perhaps those of Grcia debates before
yebra vez los de gràcia debates antes
Dallas before Dallas I used to
que dallas
do debates
yo antes que dallas hacía debate
in fact before I did my debates
de hecho antes de hacer yo mis debates
with Dallas I was already
con dallas ya ya estaba yo
debating out there only confirmed it the
debatiendo por ahí solo lo afirmó el
creator of the debates on the internet
creador de los debates en internet
in the gossip programs they have always been
en los programa del corazón siempre se
done I'm
han hecho
saying I'm saying
estoy diciendo estoy diciendo
the evaluation grace because the people
la evaluó gracia porque la gente
welcome that they know and farewell to the
bienvenida que conocen y despedida a la
family very kind
familia muy amable
from my point of view if you make him
desde mi punto de vista si le hace
record a video telling the truth
grabar un vídeo diciendo la verdad
the last thing I would like to ask you because
lo último me gustaría preguntarte porque
at the beginning the last thing that I did the
al principio lo último que yo hice las
conversations when I didn't do them
conversaciones cuando no las hice
or rather here we have been talking for a while
o sea que aquí ya llevamos un rato
hello
hola
[Music]
[Música]
saying yes
diciendo sí
and being
y siendo
first  I wouldn't like it if you don't mind
primero no me gustaría si no te importa
if I don't mind I would like to send
si no me importa me gustaría mandarte a
you the conversations and everything and then your
ti las conversaciones y todo y luego tus
sisters to your girlfriend or calling
hermanas a tu novia o llamando
directly I
directamente
don't want to publish it on the internet because
no lo quiero publicar en internet porque
the truth is that not everyone dresses
la verdad es que no se vistas de todo el
but Ivan gave many
mundo pero es que iván dio muchos
examples of many brands and diverse and
ejemplos de muchas marcas y diverso y
man lol well
hombre lol
welcome to the bar or what
pues bienvenido en el bar o sea es que
happens man the worst thing is that this one
lo que pasa tío que lo peor es que este
could have gotten into
se puede haber metido en un problema
legal trouble because publishing
legal por lo penal porque publicar
conversations in which he is a
conversaciones en los que en él es
participant and more with the intention that he
partícipe y más con la intención que lo
did it okay but with the intention that he did it
ha hecho vale pero con la intención que
is with the intention of
lo ha hecho es con la intención de
posting it and that they put it up
ponerlo y que lo ponen
could constitute a criminal offense it depends well it depends well
puede ser constitutivo de delito penal
because maybe
depende ya depende ya porque a lo mejor
as I said what he did is legal it
tal como dije lo que ha hecho es legal
may not seem shady but it is
no puede parecer turbio pero es que es
legal
legal
at least the conversations that I got out that
por lo menos las conversaciones que saco
I saw this afternoon I don't know if there are
que yo vi esta tarde no sé si habrá
others that have come out new after or
otras hayan salió nueva después o lo que
whatever but the ones that I saw of a 16 year old girl
sea pero las que yo viera de una chica
then it is legal it is shady because the
entonces es legal es turbio porque el
guy is 27 he is unfaithful to his girlfriend
tío tiene 27 es infiel a la novia
because he has a 27 year old guy where the hell is she going
porque tiene un tío de 27 dónde va
with  a 16 year old what the [ __ ] are you talking about what the
con una de 16 qué hablas
[ __ ] relationships those birds
qué relaciones esas aves
trying to flirt how disgusting god be
intentando ligar que asco dios sea
mate you like to know
colega te gusta saber
legal it was not that it was with minors under
legal no era que era con menores edad de
16 the house came out in the one that comes out of the
16 la casa salió en la que sale del
red wine the one that puts this the combination
tinto la que pone este la combinación
that exposes this is 16 so you
que expone este es de 16 entonces tú
are exposing a conversation of two
estás exponiendo una conversación de
others in which you are not a
otros dos en los que tú no eres
participant you are a third party and they are
partícipe eres un tercero y la están
publishing it in front of millions of people the
publicando ante millones de personas las
cooperations to make
cooperaciones para ponerlo de pedófilo
the other a pedophile for the pedophile it is not because it
al otro para el pedófilo no es porque no
is not pedophilia it has already been explained many
es pedofilia ya lo explicado muchas
times to make it look
veces
bad to associate his image you
para dejarlo mal para asociar su imagen
understand me
me entiende
clear you
claro
can get into trouble
se puede meter en un lío
you can say it it
puedes decirlo
depends on the country no but this
es que depende del país no pero esto
is here and not
está aquí y no
being here
estando aquí
or rather the move is that the move of what
o sea la movida es que la movida de qué
and we can look at this guy I have
y lo podemos mirar este tío me han
received conversations of his flirting is
llegado conversaciones suyas ligando es
that you have published the public audios by
que has publicado los audios públicas al
publishing an intimacy that neither goes
publicar una intimidad que a él ni le va
nor comes to him
ni le viene
16 years old nothing nothing seems much older I
16 años nada nada parece mucho mayor yo
think he thinks that we have been seen in
creo que piensa que se nos ha visto en
life like this and now since it has gone
la vida así y ahora como se ha hecho
viral viral half known that I do not  I
viral viral medio conocido que yo no
knew I've been without trust of
conocía estado sin fía de
him he's become half known because he
él se ha hecho medio conocido pues se
got on
subió
and
y
powerful
poderosos
the cards are
las cartas están
supposed not energy has not lied about
suponer no energía no ha mentido sobre
everything gave more said that if all the
todo dio más dicho que si todas las
conversations you
conversaciones
're talking to me about several things at
me estás hablando de varias cosas a la
once I'm processing the first that
vez estoy procesando la primera que
not everyone knows how to maintain everything
todos no saben mantener todo
you can cut people are not going to listen
puedes cortar gente no va a escuchar
because they have called me and it prevents me from
porque me han llamado y me impide que
the headphones if you don't listen to it
los auriculares si no lo escuchas
my mother
madre mía
for publishing put together the
por publicar juntar las bebidas
energy drinks are healthy the result
energéticas son saludables el resultado
but for publishing simply for
pero por publicar simplemente por
starting other people's conversations
comenzar conversaciones ajenas
but the issue of you having
pero el tema de que tú tengas
conversations
conversaciones
the issue of criminals
el tema de criminales
or rather your girlfriend that your girlfriend is
o sea que tu novia que tu novia
not that I have said that I have done
no es que yo he contado que he hecho
something wrong with her more than anything because the
algo mal de ella más que nada porque el
issue of that no no no no no has not sent me
tema de que no no no no no me ha mandado
conversations has not sent them to me made
conversaciones no me las ha mandado hizo
a call with him and played them to me the
una llamada con él y me las puso los
audios are not conversations they are public audios
audios no son conversaciones son audios
on twitter better these things do not
por twitter mejor estas cosas no
work better if better report better
funcionan mejor si mejor denuncia mejor
the ones on twitter by fas and so with we
los de twitter por fas y así ya con
call directly to the trial and see what is
llamamos directos al juicio y ver qué es
on twitter that he is saying report
lo de twitter que está diciendo denuncia
about what was on twitter
de por lo de twitter
that what was on twitter I will go if I were him
que lo de twitter voy a si fuera él
sincerely
sinceramente
I if I were  Well, I wouldn't have talked to
yo si fuera bueno no hubiera hablamos
minors
menores
starting there, but if I would file
empezando por ahí pero yo si le metía
a complaint against someone who publishes a
una denuncia a alguien que publica
conversation privately, I mean, one hundred
conversación en vía privada o sea cien
percent,
por cien
the day that someone not only talks to a
yo el día que alguien no sólo habla con
lot of people, the truth is, but some friend
mucha gente la verdad pero algún amigo
with whom I had a fight, I declare it published
con el que me peleé le dé por publicado
for a conversation that is mine about
por una conversación es mía de la
intimacy with private things,
intimidad con cosas privadas
but I file one on the [ __ ] with a goodbye,
pero yo le meto una al heca con un adiós
freak out,
flipa
important, I'm not going to give you my name
importante no te voy a dar mi nombre
to save money
para ahorrar
first because
primero porque
if you can't because they are conversations
si no puedes porque son conversaciones
with a minor, a bit of his life
con un menor un poco su vida
is a date for flirting with a
es una cita para el ligando por una niña
16 year old girl because not only do we think it is
de 16 porque no sólo nos parezca que es
legal and then judicially it doesn't
legal y entonces judicialmente no
matter what is moral or not, no, I don't know what
importa lo moral o no moral no no sé que
judicially it is skiing, skiing Prez,
judicialmente es el esquí el esquí pérez
the piece of [ __ ] skiing, but I should
el trozo de del esquí per lo tuve
have reported it at the time, apart from that at
que haber denunciado en su día a parte
that time it wasn't well placed,
en aquella época no estaba bien puesto
but not only that, but the piece
pero no solamente eso sino que el pedazo
of [ __ ], the pig started putting
de el cerdo se puso a meter
[ __ ] on me out there with the [ __ ]
para para joderme por ahí con la
shitty conversation, but
conversación de pero
also that conversation about him
igualmente ese a la conversación de lo
can be sued civilly,
puede haber demandar por lo civil
but third party conversations in which you
pero es que conversaciones de tercero en
are not a participant are already criminal  do you
la que no eres participe ya es por lo
understand
me entendéis
me or the 13,000 to 19,000 people I
a ti ni a 13 mil a 19 mil personas que
have here, you don't
tengo aquí las conversaciones raras no
want a judge to see these weird conversations, it
querrás que las vea un juez
seems legal, but if it is legal, that's what I'm
parezca legal pero es que si es legal es
telling you. If there were any, if they were under
lo que te digo si hubiera si fueran
16, under 16,
menores de 16 de menos de 16
if they were under 16, then this one would
si fueran de menos de 16 entonces a éste
n't be interested in reporting the other, it's
no le interesaría denunciar al otro
better to leave you more still.
mejor dejarte más quieto
23, since it's a 16-year-old line, no matter how much of an
23 que al ser una línea de 16 por más
arc they give us in this country, it's legal, which I
arco que nos dé en este país legal
think should depend a
que yo creo que eso debería depender un
little on the age of the other person. To
poco de la de la edad que tenga el otro
me, 16 seems very young to be
a mi 16 me parece muy joven para que sea
legal, that is to say, the law, the law is
legal o sea que la ley la ley te está
telling you that a guy of 50, a guy of 40,
diciendo que un tío de 50 un tío de 40
a guy of 60 can bet with a
un tío de 60 se puede apostar con una
16-year-old line. Thank you very much. Do you understand me? Do you
línea de 16 dark muchas gracias me
understand me or not? I
me entendéis o no
think that should depend on
yo creo que eso debería y en función de
the age, for example, if the law is legal from
la edad por ejemplo si la ley es legal a
16 onwards, I hope the other person
partir de 16 hasta espero que el otro
is up to, what am I telling you? 16 years old
tenga hasta que te digo yo 16 años
because he would have been
porque lo tuviera
4 or 5 years ago.  you
hace 4 o 5 años más
understand what I mean
me entendéis lo que os quiero decir
but whatever it is that is legal 16
pero que sea que sea que sea legal de 16
and that's legal it seems to me that
y punto legal me parece
if I'm 16 it should be allowed if it's
si gano 16 debería permitirse si lo
25 or under it
tiene de 25 para abajo
's a leap in the maturity of a
es que es un salto en la madurez de una
very different person you
persona muy diferente
understand it
me entendéis
's a leap in the maturity of a
es un salto en la madurez de una persona
very different person look look how it shows
muy diferente en mira mira cómo se nota
Paula that I'm practicing that I just
paula que estoy practicando que acabo de
put unintentionally I see them like
poner sin querer los veo como el
minecraft
minecraft
my person
a mi persona
nobody knows the version that I have
nadie conoce la versión que yo tengo
the same that they are 10 years apart maybe
lo mismo que se lleven 10 años a lo
a
mejor una persona de
22 year old person for a 32 year old or a 32 year old with another
22 por una de 32 o una de 32 con otra
with another 42 year old and another 50 year old with a
con otra de 42 y otra de 50 con una de
60 year old to a 16 year old with a 26 year old
60 a una de 16 con uno de 26
with one leap the life of a person once again
con un salto la vida de una persona una
I have brought the relationship of your
vez más yo he traído la relación de tu
control and the horns or whatever you want to
control y los cuernos o lo que quieras
call it behind the table to
llamarlo detrás de la mesa para
deny that what it is
desmentir eso de qué es
if it is a minor and the age difference
si es menor y la diferencia de edad
between one and the other is more than four years it
entre uno y otro es más de cuatro años
is illegal despite the age of
es ilegal a pesar de la edad de
consent
consentimiento
sure sure love and so
seguro seguro amar y así
then I  you're saying that one of 21
entonces me estás diciendo que uno de 21
no that's not like mari
no eso no es así a mari
that's not like
eso no es así
I was 25 and he's 34 every pore from 25 to 34
yo tenía 25 y el 34 cada poro de 25 a 34
even if it's almost a decade it's not the
aunque sea casi una década no es lo
same from 25 to 34 as maybe from
mismo de 25 a 34 que a lo mejor d
15 to 24
15 a 24
you know it's not like that here so then you
entiende no es así aquí entonces
're telling me that it would be
entonces me estás diciendo que sería
illegal for a
ilegal
21 year old to go out with someone of 16
uno de 21 que se fuera con alguien de 16
and it's not illegal at
y no lo es
all those corners like that in Argentina that's how it is
nada esas esquinas así en argentina así
but
pero
the
la
people who
gente que
can comment if they are subscribed what it
puede comentar si está suscrita lo que
means is that the people
quiere decir que la gente
of the
del
channel
canal
before the day
antes de que el día
ml you
ml
consider
consideráis
in the people
en la gente
now
ahora
[Music]
[Música]
if you
si
consider that he can have photos of
consideráis que puede tener fotos de
a friend it's like they are of the 9 in a ball
alguna amiga es como sean del 9 en bola
as if it were a vehicle and how they look it
como si sea vehículo y cómo se ven
seems to consider is that that is being
parece considerar es que eso es ser
unfaithful it
infiel
depends on the context it
depende del contexto
depends on the context but let's go
depende del contexto pero vamos
the majority of occasions no in several
la mayoría de ocasiones no en varias
occasions asking they are asking for
ocasiones pidiendo le están pidiendo
everything that has been seen in these
todo lo que se ha visto en estas
asking with the tone that they are
pidiendo con el tono que le están
asking for the photo in that cooperation it is
pidiendo la la foto en esa cooperación
seen if it were like I said that of
es que se ve si fuera como dije la del
supercharly if he went to jail  She's been in
supercharly si a la cárcel que le lleva
Dallas for almost a decade x d
casi una década a dallas x d
these cartoons talk for two days it has
estas viñetas hablan dos días no tiene
nothing to do with it she's talking about the age of
nada que ver está hablando de la edad de
consent
consentimiento
being so so young even that she enters
siendo tan tan joven incluso que se meta
the club you even asked her week
en el club incluso le preguntaste semana
to week she told you I'm with my friend and
a semana te dijo estoy con mi amiga y
power and have photos of pressuring the
poder y tener fotos de presionar lo
same or I mean you can have a photo that I
mismo o sea tú puedes tener alguna foto
tell you
que te digo yo
or a bikini photo that you have with
o una foto en bikini que tenga tú con
her or that you like because she looks pretty or
ella o que te guste porque salga guapa o
whatever know another thing is that you in
lo que sea saber otra cosa es que tú en
that conversation I am informing her that we are
esa conversación le estoy informando de
going to see in person sometimes
que dar vamos a ver en persona a veces
how it sounded in the audio to see if
cómo se escuchaba en el audio a ver si
in person it is the same this well the two of us
en persona es igual este pues las dos
send you a clear photo but that photo we
te mando una foto clara pero esa foto no
were not talking about that subject because
estábamos hablando de ese tema porque
thanks
gracias
at no time does that girl next to me
en ningún momento esa chica de al lado
know that she is sending photos like that to
sabe que ella está mandando fotos así a
people which is why when I said the two it
la gente por lo cual cuando dije las dos
is because I know that the girl who was
es porque sé que la chica que estaba
talking about the conversation with her and she
hablando de la conversación con ella y
said then which way in photos
se dijo entonces para qué lado en fotos
on site they will send me because the girls do
en sitio me mandaran porque las chicas
not know
no saben
what you tell me
que me cuentas
at all times the girl told me that
en todo momento me dijo la chica que
nobody in her environment knows that she sends
nadie de su entorno sabe que ella manda
photos and consumes diagonals and from some
fotos y consum diagonales y de unas
photos she said look  I'm in the living room with
fotos le dijo mira estoy en el salón con
my dad and my brother with my hands
mi padre y con mi hermano con mis manos
and that we can't give you anything and then one
y que no podemos darte nada y luego un
day he came to his room to his room that's
día llegó a su cuarto a su cuarto es
when they send me pictures telling me
cuando ya me mandan fotos diciéndome
listener sent to the long background in the
oyente mandó al fondo largo del en el
room because because nobody that environment and
cuarto porque porque nadie ese entorno y
that to me I care about
eso a mí me importa
your adventures
tus aventuras
the example matters to me
por eso me importa el ejemplo
[Music]
[Música]
and the guy lends himself to a debate man
y el tío se presta a un debate tío
the guy
el tío
who was teaching I
que enseñaba
think looking closely at the monster boy it's
creo que mirando bien al chico monster
clear that it affects taking
queda claro que afecta a tomar en exceso
those drinks in excess face with your eyes wide
esas bebidas cara con los ojos bien
closed and sticking out your tongue face with your
cerrados y sacando la lengua cara con
eyes wide closed and sticking out your
los ojos bien cerrados y sacando la
tongue face with your eyes wide closed and
lengua cara con los ojos bien cerrados y
taking out the law of certain voices with it
sacando la ley de ciertas voces con ella
denies what you main argument
desmiente lo que tú argumento principal
Emiliano with nobody is not very something nobody
emiliano con nadie ni es muy algo nadie
or anything of what was done
ni nada de lo hecho
exposes
expone
said
dijo
that he was taking pills with a
que se estaba haciendo pastillas con una
smile is what he is saying has not
sonrisa es lo que está diciendo no ha
started to
empezado
see to see do you consider infidelity do you
a ver a ver consideráis infidelidad
consider infidelity to
consideráis infidelidad
follow a girl in the ifai and that you
seguir a una chica en el ifai y que te
like her photos and that you make some
gusten sus fotos y que te hagas algún
arrangement with the photos are the best
apaño con las fotos son los mejores
listen to me that we  gave
escúchame eso nos dio
but of course
pero claro
there are times when circumstances schedules and
hay veces que circunstancias horarios y
things well you can't vent every day
cosas pues no puede todos los días
and that has to be renewed if you do
desahogarte y eso hay que renovarlo si
n't feel that there I
no siente que hay
can give you a lot of pain in
te puedo dar dolores de un huevo en
men and not because of gave love
hombres y no por dio cariño
ask for photos not to see if they do it or
pedirle fotos no para ver si realizan o
not
no
but of course the conversations that you are going to
pero claro que las conversaciones que
show will not be live and
vas a enseñar no serán don't live and
if the girlfriend does it I would consider it
si la novia lo hace lo consideraría
infidelity
infidelidad
and we already have it here in front of you if it
y ya lo tenemos aquí delante de usted si
's with Paula Echevarra it doesn't count even if there is
es con paula echevarría no cuenta ni
contact Frank Olcina I already have that I have
aunque haya contacto frank olcina eso ya
talked about it I have
lo tengo lo tengo hablado lo tengo
talked about it in case the case arises
hablado por si se diera el caso
it's like saying see no why not what
es como decir que ver no por qué no qué
nonsense let's see but it's that you
bobada a ver pero es que tú de vez en
yourself
cuando a ti mismo
need some images from time to time we don't
necesitas unas imágenes no
need the images it's a requirement
necesitamos las imágenes es un requisito
there are people who have imagination and there are
hay gente que tiene imaginación y hay
times when it gets you very excited and you don't
veces que te coge muy para arriba y no
need images or oxidase generates
necesita ni imágenes ni oxidasa genera
a speaker pont but there are times when you
un parlante pont pero hay veces que
need some images
necesitas unas imágenes
you have to request it you will have to do
tienes que solicitarla tendrá que hacer
the process it doesn't have paperwork
el proceso no lleva un papeleo
on call you don't have much money he
en llamada no tiene mucho dinero
called me
me llamó
and
y
said hey he said hey if you decide I
me dijo oye me dijo oye si decide yo
always need material and I read that and
siempre necesito material y yo leí que y
where to  where does dad turn to the
de dónde a dónde recurre papá el
material
material
get 700 euros if he wants
consigue 700 euros si quiere
we meet for a day and I don't know how much
quedamos un día y no sé qué en cuanto
that money I'm not going to pay first
ese dinero no voy a pagar lo primero
because I don't want to and second because I don't
porque no quiero y segundo porque no
have it if he wants when I go to Seville he
tengo yo si quiere cuando vaya sevilla
denied half but he told me one day today
negó la mitad pero me dijo en su día hoy
the atheist money if he has this 102
el ateo dinero si tiene este 102
I think
yo creo
from an apartment and man hahahahaha
de piso y hombre jajajajaja
thanks nevado but I think he has repeated
gracias nevado pero creo que ha repetido
messages
mensajes
I turn to my contacts and seriously read
yo recurre a mis contactos y serio lee
but jolie here contacts
pero jolie aquí contactos
listen to me 300 euros he asked him for a
escúchame 300 euros le pidió por una
photo and the hate appears when he
foto y que aparece el odio cuando le
asked him for 300 euros their libido went down
pidió 300 euros se les bajó la libido
game they don't even pay anymore and
partido ya ni pagan y
300 euros three empty cans
300 euros tres latas vacías
300 lots showed his soul if necessary
300 lotes enseñó el alma si hace falta
[Music]
[Música]
I create material
yo creo material
you create material it's late it has sun and
tú creas material es tardío tiene sol y
funk
funk
you know what happens I'm going to upload the
sabéis qué pasa que voy a ir subiendo el
news okay he thinks it's going to be
noticiero vale me cree que va a ser más
longer he the
largo él
[ __ ] with the message of being there was
el del mensaje de estar di estaba
uploading the news so I'm going to
subiendo el noticiero así que lo voy a
put it suddenly that we continue watching the
poner súbita que seguimos viendo el
debate
debate
I went to the army it's without checking it  I'm going to
me fui al ejército es sin revisarlo lo
upload because now check out a
voy a subir porque ahora revisa un
newscast I'm going to trust success and I'm
noticiero me voy a fiar de éxito y lo
going to upload it
voy a subir
watch out this is the drama your ver 5 is already going to
ojo que este es el drama tu ver 5 ya es
see the debate we're not going to see it all
a ver el debate no lo vamos a ver entero
but the day of course is that the
pero el día por supuesto es que en la
difference between you and her is that she
diferencia entre tú y ella es que ella
is single and you and I study this degree
está soltera y tú y estudio este grado
cultivation of this not because it doesn't matter if you
cultivo de esto no porque no importe si
are already excited she may have
ya está excitado ella está pueda haber
bid but if you take away the affected ones
licitado pero si le quitas los afectados
or you have wanted to accept it means that
o has querido aceptar significa que no
your girlfriend does not reside which is what I'm
resida tu novia que es lo que te estoy
telling you it's and it is my argument that
diciendo ya está y es mi argumento que
if
si
one says things that one does not think it is not that they
uno dice cosas que uno no piensa que no
have a moment of heat
es que tiene un momento de calentón
dapple the problem knows that of course in
tordilla el problema sabe que claro en
a moment of heat there are people who are the ones who
un momento de calentón hay gente que es
say things that they do not think the
el que dice cosas que no piensan el
problem is when they have the moment of
problema es cuando tienen el momento de
heat all day knowing when you
calentón todo el día saber cuándo
expect when is born we want this the
esperas cuando nace queremos esto el
chronic heat lying to her the thing is that of
calentón crónico mentirle la la cosa es
course in what she says let's see that at
que claro en lo que dice a ver que yo en
the moment I am hot and I am with to
el momento estoy caliente y estoy con
give the hand and I say verbal fight before
echar la mano y digo lucha verbal ante
new girlfriend agreement the best of
nuevo acuerdo de novia lo más bueno de
nobody
nadie
already then when the stop that happens many
ya luego cuando la para eso pasa muchas
times
veces
and because the mail  Monster has a
y porque el mail monster tiene voz de
squeaky voice and the littlest kid has an
y el chaval más pequeño tiene voz
email voice things in life maybe it happens a
de mail cosas de la vida tal vez se pasa
lot of times you know plan you get really
muchas veces saben plan te vienes muy
high really horny you forget you have a
arriba muy caliente se te olvida que
partner you forget everything and then
tienes pareja se te olvida todo y luego
at the moment that it's already cool it had cut
en el momento que ya cool había cortado
all the poison the mind is another the mind
todo el veneno la mente es otra la mente
seems to think differently who
como que como que piensa diferente
owns the one who owns the moment of
que posee el que posee el momento del
heat knows then how to let it go
calentón sabe luego hacerse los suelta
and the vote well the mountain
y el voto pues el monte también
can also be monster also also [ __ ] up
puede ser monster también también
you're taking 7 I showed a day well I already
te estás tomando 7 mostré al día pues ya
told you no
te digo no
7 then the kid is going to live
7 luego el chaval se va a vivir
but I have
pero yo tengo
next to
al lado
this we are the TV
de esto somos la tele
once every four months
una vez cada cuatro meses
once every four months and you have to
una vez cada cuatro meses y te tienes
move the zambomba from time to time
que mover la zambomba de vez en cuando
listen to me don't act like you now being
escúchame no te las de a tú ahora de
neat don't act like you now being neat
pulcro no te las de ahora de pulcro
because listen to me
porque escúchame
[Music]
[Música]
once every four months seeing your
una vez cada cuatro meses viendo a tu
girlfriend you have to move the drum you don't have to
novia te tienes que menear el tambo no
have let's go some special gloves
tiene que tener vamos unos guantes
toys magazines no I mean like you have to
juguetes revistas no o sea en plan
have the subscription to the
tienes que tener la suscripción a las
pages they are like to see a
páginas están en plan para ir viendo
different ass every day
culo diferente cada día
three times  a year already chunga and
tres veces al año chamizo ya chunga y
there you bought a reality show do deza a
ahí te compraste una reality do deza una
real and real one and two of those dolls and
real y real y dos de esas muñecas y
conditions man xavi no there
condiciones hombre xavi no ahí tendría
the subject should be allowed already
que estar permitido el tema ya
I think you're sending me
yo creo que me estás mandando
jolie I hope this lawsuit is not
jolie espero que esta demanda no sea
material like yours as
material del que el tuyo como material
previous support material
apoyo anterior
again
otra vez
weighing down with this direct true this
lastrando con este directo verdad este
direct can cost us a ban on
directo nos puede costar un baneo en
tweet
tweet
a baleo on tweet a ban on youtube not
un baleo en tuit un baneo en youtube no
monetize the same in divorce too
monetizar lo mismo en divorcio también
but the thing would be
pero la cosa sería
or rather they ask team team are
o sea le preguntan team team son
teenagers
adolescentes
or like the other guy
o como era el otro tipo que
but the thing would be
pero la cosa sería
and that they
y
are mature
que son maduras
mature
maduritas
the thing would be
la cosa sería
and disguised as a keyboard player later on
y disimulado de teclista después en el
today's news
noticiero de hoy
or over 18 but it seems
o sea mayor de 18 pero que parezca
even though they have let's
aunque tengan
say it seems like they have
digamos que parece que tengan
more than the others they thought
más que los otros de pensaban
buf he
buf
says over 18
dice mayores de 18
t to a thousand but total
t a mil pero total
t to a thousand but total there are a thousand
t a mil pero total haber mil
when we talk about me
cuando hablamos de mí
we're talking about 1001
hablamos de 1001
the ones that I like I'm
las que me gustan a mí de
forty and forty something but but of
cuarenta y cuarenta y pico pero pero
course we're not talking about Carmen de Mairena
claro no hablamos del carmen de mairena
or something  like that when we talk about a thousand it's getting out
o algo así no cuando hablamos de mil nos
of hand no either but
está yendo de las manos no tampoco pero
look at what you say
que fíjate lo que dices
and with the face you say it the important thing
y con la cara que lo dice lo importante
is the face look at the face
es la cara mira en la cara
very screwed this is very shady it's
muy esto es muy turbio
like it
es como
says 18 as if saying that they are of legal
dice 18 como diciendo que sean mayores
age but that they seem like the wanted
de edad pero que parezcan la quería
rule for which it goes worse let's
regla para la que va peor
say that they have
digamos que tengan
18 really
con 18 veras
over 18 to save my ass that I'm
mayores 18 para salvar el culo que estoy
in public
en público
but that it seems that I have
pero que parezca que tenga
[Music] let's
[Música]
say that for them to have
digamos que para que tengan
that 18 and I said it as if saying that I can't say that that I ca
eso 18 y lo decía como diciendo eso que
n't say
eso que no puedo decirlo
if you're going to say that don't forget
si tú vas a decir que no se te olvide
this guy came out in the wine river it's wide
este tipo salió en el río wine es ancho
the sancho
el sancho
that area more than for this clip
esa zona más que por este clip
I don't want it, let's say not in the
no lo quiero yo la vera vamos ni en el
wei river or anywhere
río wei ni ninguna parte
to this one it was damaging for the wine river what do you
a este dañaba para el río wine qué os
think I mean it's the salsa singer in the
parece o sea es el salsero en el río
wine river kaka but this guy yeah let's
wine kaká pero este tío sí
see if you're going to say 18 but that they
a ver si tú vas a decir de 18 pero que
seem like they have
parezcan que tengan
then he tells us 1818 and he's going to say something and he's
luego nos dice 1818 y va a decir algo y
going to tell me no
va a decirme no
very well go ahead
muy bien adelante
very well the walk
muy bien el ande
and you're going to say less
y vas a decir menos
that it seems that they have and you're going to say
que parece que tengan y vas a decir
less if it doesn't tell us that it seems that they
menos si no nos dice que parece que
come well
vengan
[Music]
[Música]
yes I'm
sí
glad that she
que me alegro que
's ready or anything but I'm
está lista ni nada pero te estoy
telling you that that denies growing and
diciendo que eso desmiente creciendo y
that's what I'm saying
eso es lo que yo estoy diciendo ya está
the boot is already of being a couple a relationship
la bota de ser una pareja una relación
of relationships I don't give a damn about your relationship I
de relaciones me la suda tu relación te
'm telling you that you are faithful and for
estoy diciendo que eres fiel y por lo
which yes no
cual sí no
because you have done it in the past
porque lo has hecho en el pasado
after an assessment but that she is
tras una valoración pero que está
trying to look for I wrote we don't do it
intentando buscar escribí no lo hacemos
with me because because you get together
conmigo porque porque te la xunta
then what she wants with the world is
entonces lo que quiere con el mundo está
trying to look for my girlfriend to look for
intentando buscar que mi novia se busque
me my
conmigo
mother anything is that this is
madre mía cualquier cosa es que este es
the danger that today anyone
el peligro de que hoy en día cualquiera
creates an account and becomes famous
se crea una cuenta y se hace famoso
anyone people many times without
cualquiera gente muchas veces sin
education without respect for others
educación sin respeto por los demás
illiterate
analfabetos
who lack respect for the privacy of
que falta el respeto a la intimidad de
everyone who defame who slander
todo el mundo que difaman que calumnia
people like that uses their power
gente así que utiliza su poder
because it is published but I nobody knows her
porque se publica pero yo no la conoce
and
nadie y
since not with which I am like
puesto que no con lo cual yo estoy como
but I do not want to pay them saying is that
pero no quiero pagarlos diciendo es que
on some occasion on some occasion my
en alguna ocasión en alguna ocasión mi
boyfriend has also stayed  with some
novio también ha quedado con algún
boy friend of his
chaval amigo suyo
for Michel and I also stays alive
para míchel y yo también queda con vida
because of not arriving this question
por la no llegada esta pregunta
and
y
now he says it's
ahora dice que
going to be one night and sometimes we have said I get
va a ser una noche y a veces hemos dicho
angry
yo me cabreo
what are you
qué
doing he
estás haciendo
stops talking to me
me deja de hablar
so that he will have in his head all over the
para que tendrá en la cabeza a todos al
internet your private relationships but the
internet tus relaciones privadas pero el
fact that your argument that I
hecho de que no de que tu argumento de
am faithful is a lie because it is
que soy fiel sea mentira porque lo es
because we have
porque tenemos
lies everything that
miente todo lo que
at no time we are and do not continue
en ningún momento somos y no sigas
talking that you are putting your relationship
hablando que estás poniendo tu relación
and we hope that you also have to have a
y esperamos que también hay que tener
certain maturity to not get angry with your
cierta madurez para no enfadarse con su
partner for seeing not because of these types of photos it
pareja por ver no por este tipo de fotos
is only entertainment my girlfriend
sólo es entretenimiento mi novia
now
ahora
my girlfriend and I have a peace of
mi novia y yo nos pasamos paz de
better people physically clear
personas mejores físicamente claro
exactly if you are not doing anything
exactamente si no estás haciendo nada
wrong you
malo
do not hide from your partner pages that you see
no ocultas a tu pareja páginas que veas
or photos that you have on your phone you
o fotos que tengas en el móvil me
understand me it came out I can have that a
entiendes salió puedo tener que una
bookstore of Paula Echevarra sticks
librería de palos de paula echevarría
quietly and the computer I have my little
tranquilamente y el ordenador tengo mi
folder of Paula Echevarra and nothing happens
carpetita de paula echevarría y no pasa
such that it does not have a fat no craft
tal que no tiene una grasa no craft
Luisa Mainou this is why I like older people those
luisa mainou por esto me gustan mayores
of my age are like these
los de mi edad son como estos
treatments
tratamientos
exactly Jolie you
exactamente jolie
have given him the perfect example cry  It's that
le has puesto el ejemplo perfecto llorís
Paula Echevarra, many Paula,
es que la paula echevarría muchas paula
at the moment I have done something that my girlfriend
en el momento he hecho algo que mi novia
could consider unfaithful
podría considerar el infiel
because you are telling the girl
porque le estás diciendo a la chavala
when they are giving her all the photos that I have
cuando le están dando todas fotos que
the girlfriend next to me
tengo la novia al lado
that I have the girlfriend next to the photos
que tengo la novia al lado de las fotos
of the girl
de la chica
those are things that I do not have to get involved in of
eso son cosas que yo no te tienes que
course of course but I have
por supuesto por supuesto pero yo lo he
brought it to the table to demonstrate that the
traído a la mesa para demostrar que el
government does
gobierno
not have its
no tiene su
late ex different companies
tardía empresas diferentes
14 years
14 años
but I have brought it to the table to demonstrate that
pero yo lo he traído para demostrar que
the government
el gobierno
of 14 years
de 14 años
please let me talk to him
por favor déjame hablar con él
I never says that being with the 14 I
yo nunca dice que estando con el 14 yo
what I have published in a girl of 16
lo que he publicado en una niña de 16
that is not illegal no but it is very strange
que no es ilegal no pero es muy raro
you are 27 years old you are 11 years older then
tienes 27 años le sacas 11 años entonces
I have brought it out as I tell you for the
yo lo he sacado como te lo digo por
twentieth time that the people of direct
vigésima vez que la gente de directo
are bored of hearing it
estar aburrida de escucharlo
that I bring it to you in sight to
que yo te lo traigo a la vista para
demonstrate that your argument that you are
demostrar que tu argumento de que eres
faithful you that you have a girlfriend that you
fiel te que tienes novia de que
ask about the boyfriend because you are
preguntas lo del novio porque tienes
afraid that her boyfriend will come to you I know it is a lie it is a
miedo de que te venga su novio sé que es
lie
mentira es mentira
explain what I believe I believe  I'm
explicar lo que yo creo yo creo
not playing with you that
no te estoy jugando que
the attention of the
la atención de la
direction
dirección
thanks welcome and now and that we
gracias bienvenidos y ahora y que te
saw you as a person of power and they have
veíamos una persona de poder y te han
come to you and you have taken advantage of
venido y tú has aprovechado
the pull and relationships the same think the
el tirón y relaciones lo mismo piensan
same and after 50 to stay following
lo mismo y luego de 50 quedar siguiendo
the expressiveness of the follow the three and I
la expresividad del sigue las tres y me
realized that the 3 and 6 would be self
di cuenta que las 3 y 6 serían auto
beautiful between them I realized that they were
bellos entre ellas me di cuenta que eran
false diverse are already holding of
falsas diversas ya están sosteniendo de
the block the three sheets because I
las bloquear las tres sábanas porque me
realized that what they were doing
di cuenta que lo que estaban haciendo
because because the z and her house surely
porque porque la z y su casa seguramente
the house of one of the girls
la casa de una de las chicas
failed has been that I have answered
fallo ha sido que he respondido todo el
everyone and I should not have faced the
mundo y no debería haber enfrentando el
world I have already you have arrived many times today it
mundo yo ya me habéis muchas veces hoy
should not be so narrow
llegado no debería ser tan angosta está
energy is involved another thing that I am going to
metida energía otra cosa que voy a
tell you by the way
decirle por cierto
and
y
to
a
many people what surprises me is that it
mucha gente lo que me sorprende es que
is only conchitas because it is no
sólo sea conchitas porque es ningún
boy has come out to ask him what I
chico ha salido con preguntarle qué le
asked him what do you want a photo because
pregunté qué quieres una foto porque
conscience I assure you that they are
conciencia te aseguro que son
mostly boys then
mayoritariamente chicos entonces
a
un
message a boy sent you a message in
mensaje un chaval te mande un mensaje en
April
abril
I wait for
espero
the sea and in July and you did not answer
el mar y en julio y no le contestaste a
any of them because I did not
ninguno porque yo no
send you a message in December
te mando un mensaje en diciembre
in the time
en el tiempo
since  35 years ago
desde hace 35
I also have followers
yo también tengo seguidores
but I won't
pero no te
respond to the power because when you talk
responderá al poder porque cuando hables
to 56 they write back they hurt you and 66
con 56 vuelven a escribir te hieren y 66
and it can't get down completely well
y no puede llegar abajo del todo pues se
the time has passed
me ha pasado el momento
to
de
leave this when you respond to a
dejar esto cuando tú respondes a un
message of the requests [ __ ] let's
mensaje de las solicitudes chorradas a
see let's see
ver vamos a ver
in the trending on twitter
en el trending de twitter
what a shame what a
qué pena
shame about to
qué pena lo de a
this man of god who was
lo de este hombre de dios que se han
found dead today he was there
encontrado muerto hoy día estuvo allí
working it was his monologue he was in
trabajando ha sido su monólogo estaba en
Orlando
orlando
at 62 years old
con 62 años
then your uncle I was a super fan and I am
luego de tu tío era súper fan y lo soy
of this series god
de esta serie dios
of this series god how in fact I
de esta serie dios como de hecho me
swallowed it 4 or 5 years ago they released the
tragué hace 4 o 5 años sacaron la el
remake of this Fuller House and we're going to
remake este de madre forzosas y lo vamos
patiently I saw all the
pacientemente me lo vi todos los
chapters the first day how is
capítulo el primer día
life how is
como es la vida
life it's
cómo es la vida de
no longer trending
ya no está en tendencia
to those of us who are trending
a los que nos en tendencia
in the yolk blocked I wanted I'll stay
en el yema bloqueado yo quería me quedo
my dead
mi muerto
at
al
50% because of the anger because I would take the
50% por el cabreo pues le quitaba la
can away and so let's try it
lata y así que vamos a probarla
[Music]
[Música]
that by the way if you kill
que por cierto si matas
leaves the  priority and I really do
deja la prioridad y yo de verdad
n't have to go downstairs for my things
no tienen que bajar abajo para mis cosas
yet to take some of yours so for
aún algo de lo suyo así que para
the worst look how it can sound but at
lo peor mira que puede sonar pero al
least we're going to stop
menos vamos a parar
we did
nos realizó
in my life
en mi vida
your dear kiss or anything let's
tu querido beso ni nada
see this
a ver este
Viking in the [ __ ] best series
vikingo en la mejor serie
definitely in the guide is crazy
definitivamente en el guía está mal de
we're not telling him
no le vamos
Qatar is impossible to win in Extremadura
qatar se gana imposible en extremadura
for your age
para tu edad
here there was energy so there was energy energy
aquí quedó energía así quedó energía
after mixing them moster
energía tras mezclarlas moster sabor
minor flavor with the I showed the flavor not even two
menor con la mostré el sabor ni dos
versions
versiones
photos
fotos
[Music]
[Música]
m
m
I also have a halo of energy beautiful let's
yo también me un halo de energía guapa
see all those who are here
a ver todos los que están aquí en
live girls girls
directos chicas chicas
girl that you are here live
chica que estés aquí en directo
look at your dm with energy to see if you
mirad vuestros dm con energía a ver si
have a dm of him
tenéis algún dm de él
[Laughs]
[Risas]
the one with the [ __ ] ear
la de oreja de
something is justifying energy
algo está justificando a energía
and simple you
y sencillo
can see that they are different
se puede ver que son diferentes
[Laughs]
[Risas]
ah
ah
dude of murky
tío de turbio
[Music]
[Música]
how murky god
que turbio dios
and now
y ahora
when you're going to cut your neck dude
cuando te vas a cortar el pescuezo tío
rpp then they are giving me
rpp luego me están dando
[Laughs] let's
[Risas]
see I'm going to see what I'm going to
a ver voy a ver qué es lo que voy a
remove
quitar
and right now that I have the tweet -rival
y ahora mismo que tengo el tuit -rival
in no time I'm
dentro de nada
going to see what it is that I knew well
voy a ver qué es lo que sabía bien
publish the video
publicar el vídeo
I'm going to publish the video of drama your
voy a publicar el vídeo de drama tu
truth in a second
verdad en un segundo
[Music] let's
[Música]
see drama your verse title
a ver drama tu verso título
in the
en el
energy
energía
married to
casado con
minors
menores
dallas for
dallas ara
a
una
movie
película
ok I'll
vale
upload the drama tummers now the index and I'll
subo el drama tummers ya el índice y lo
review it later ok now I'll
revisaré luego vale
put the index then I'll review it
ya el índice lo pongo luego lo revisaré
then I'm going to put it it
luego lo voy a poner
's the drama tuber 4 careful eye in 55 the
es el drama tuber 4 ojo cuidado en 55 el
fifth the 5th the fifth I
quinto el 5º el quinto
put the thumbnail that I think I
le pongo la miniatura que creo que la
download or not
descarga o no
the novel downloaded deeper
la novela descargada más honda
or to sprout the thumbnail god
o a brotar la miniatura dios
all over the thumbnail and I
por toda la miniatura y
put some rich ads and then I
le pongo unos anuncios rico y luego
check the video I trust a lot a lot to
revisó el vídeo me fío mucho mucho a
street or in the nba
calle o en la nba
jolie that what they are awakening a
jolie que lo que están despertando un
little passions
poco de pasiones
is successful taken out the bouquet shot me has made
es exitosa sacado el ramo tirme ha hecho
the video in nothing it
el vídeo en nada
seems to me that they have put the yellow man it
me parece que han puesto al amarillo tío
seems to me that they have put light yellow
me parece haber puesto amarillo claro
as energy
como de energía
they show yellow god sure I'm
se muestran amarillos dios seguro
not saying a green they have put them in
no digo un verdejo les han puesto en
green guys
verde chavales
and the notifications just jumped
y me acaba de saltar las notificaciones
and  here recommended
y aquí recomendado
those mixed batteries welcome to another
esas mixta baterías bienvenidos a otra
installment of this saturated audio
entrega de esta saturado el audio sin
unintentionally because this afternoon having the mic
querer porque esta tarde tener el micro
saturated and success does not realize they will not be
saturado y éxito no se da cuenta no la
able to fix it okay
van a poder arreglar vale
there you have the video
ahí tenéis el vídeo
thank goodness you removed it because in a meme
menos mal lo quitaste porque en un meme
of the subject if a photo jumped out at me n px of
del tema si me saltó una foto n px de
clear I was watching it
claro me lo estaba viendo yo
to see what is that of quesada
a ver qué es lo de quesada
in a way that it alarms to swallow the
de manera que se alarme a tragar el
whole video
vídeo entero
grandpa we have to train questions
abuelo tenemos que entrenarnos preguntas
I can't train I have the night
yo no puedo entrenar tengo la noche
making the script and recording of the
haciendo el guión y grabando del bien
main good tomorrow we train that of
principal mañana entrenamos lo de
quesada the wines tomorrow less man to
quesada los vinos mañana menos tío para
finish wants deal
terminar quiere trato
[Music]
[Música]